<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Digital Dodgeball</title>
    <link>https://jrembold.github.io/WUPhys-CodeComp/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Digital Dodgeball</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 14:30:25 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jrembold.github.io/WUPhys-CodeComp/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>End of Fall Season</title>
      <link>https://jrembold.github.io/WUPhys-CodeComp/post/fallseason/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 14:30:25 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrembold.github.io/WUPhys-CodeComp/post/fallseason/</guid>
      <description>The Fall Season of Digital Dodgeball will be ending on Tuesday the 16th! Get your bot submitted by the end of Monday for a chance to come out atop the leaderboards! The victor will get a prize as well as their name immortalized in the Hall of Fame to the left. So basically huge stakes. :)
A few bug fixes have gone in recently, so make sure you grab the latest files if you haven&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Patch Update!</title>
      <link>https://jrembold.github.io/WUPhys-CodeComp/post/halloweenpatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 15:53:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrembold.github.io/WUPhys-CodeComp/post/halloweenpatch/</guid>
      <description>I recently pushed out some updates to fix a few issues and add another. Explanations are worked into the documentation page, but changes included:
 Increasing the radius of the ping functionality. It will now get information on everything in a 8 square radius. Increased the default map size to 20x20 and the default max number of obstacles to 10. These are of course still configurable, but these will be the defaults that the leaderboards use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documentation Updated</title>
      <link>https://jrembold.github.io/WUPhys-CodeComp/post/docsposted/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 15:55:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrembold.github.io/WUPhys-CodeComp/post/docsposted/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve moved the readme material from the GitHub page over to the Documentation link to the left! I also went through and cleaned up and fleshout out some of the descriptions. If there is some bit of information that you&amp;rsquo;d like to know that I haven&amp;rsquo;t included, please let me know so I can get it added! Thanks!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started Guide Posted!</title>
      <link>https://jrembold.github.io/WUPhys-CodeComp/post/guideposted/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 13:58:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrembold.github.io/WUPhys-CodeComp/post/guideposted/</guid>
      <description>The About and Getting Started pages to the website have been updated. Getting Started now walks you through the process of getting started creating your first bot, from downloading the needed files to running the game server. I&amp;rsquo;ll be writing and updating the documentation section next!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Website Created!</title>
      <link>https://jrembold.github.io/WUPhys-CodeComp/post/newwebsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrembold.github.io/WUPhys-CodeComp/post/newwebsite/</guid>
      <description>Celebrate! This new and improved website has been created with the intention of streamlining and better explaining the logic and ideas behind Digital Dodgeball! Hopefully it serves as a better introduction to the game and as a source of ideas for new players to investigate.
Useful links about getting started, documentation for the game, and ideas for bot algorithms can be found on the sidebar.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>